[English subtitles are available]
[الترجمة الإنجليزية متوفرة]
[I Belonged To Your World]
[أنتمي إلى عالمك]
Qi Yue.
تشي يو.
Your personal delivery man.
رجل التوصيل الشخصي الخاص بك.
Two portions of tofu pudding, one without peanuts.
حصتين من بودنغ التوفو ، واحدة بدون فول سوداني.
Why two portions?
لماذا جزئين؟
Am I a glutton in your heart?
هل أنا شره في قلبك؟
One is for Qi Shuo.
واحد من أجل Qi Shuo.
Love me, love my cousin. You are worth praising.
أحبني ، أحب ابن عمي.  أنت تستحق الثناء.
I made a daily date schedule
لقد قمت بعمل جدول زمني يومي
in order to reduce variables.
من أجل تقليل المتغيرات.
[Daily Date Schedule]
[جدول التاريخ اليومي]
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Are you running away from home again?
هل تهرب من المنزل مرة أخرى؟
You even made a schedule for dating.
حتى أنك وضعت جدولًا للمواعدة.
Good for you.
جيدة بالنسبة لك.
Where are you going, Qi Shuo?
إلى أين أنت ذاهب ، تشي شو؟
Moving out.
أرحل.
I'm single.
أنا أعزب.
I'm not going to stay here to be a third wheel.
لن أبقى هنا لأكون عجلة ثالثة.
Moving out?
أرحل؟
Where?
أين؟
You don't know anyone here.
أنت لا تعرف أحدا هنا.
Isn't Lu Xiao a human?
أليس لو شياو إنسانًا؟
Isn't Deng Shuling a human?
أليس دينغ شولينج إنساناً؟
I mean
أعني
how you are gonna live alone if you move out.
كيف ستعيش بمفردك إذا خرجت.
Why are you acting like my mom?
لماذا تتصرف مثل أمي؟
I am your mother.
انا والدتك.
Wait.
انتظر.
You can move out.
يمكنك الخروج.
Have you found a place?
هل وجدت مكانا؟
I'll stay there as long as I find a proper place.
سأبقى هناك طالما وجدت مكانًا مناسبًا.
No matter what decision you have made,
بغض النظر عن القرار الذي اتخذته ،
you have to listen to your girlfriend.
عليك الاستماع إلى صديقتك.
Just say it.
فقط قلها.
Today's schedule is
جدول اليوم هو
to find a house.
للعثور على منزل.
[Everyone Is Lonely Episode 16]
[الجميع وحيد الحلقة 16]
Trust me.
ثق بي.
Why do you want to move out?
لماذا تريد الخروج؟
To keep a distance from her.
للحفاظ على مسافة منها.
Although I'm her cousin,
على الرغم من أنني ابن عمها ،
don't you feel uncomfortable
ألا تشعر بعدم الارتياح
if your girlfriend lives with a man
إذا كانت صديقتك تعيش مع رجل
every day?
كل يوم؟
I don't.
أنا لا.
It's just a little weird.
إنه مجرد غريب بعض الشيء.
Weird?
غريب؟
What is weird?
ما هو الغريب؟
It's weird that you suddenly want to move out.
من الغريب أنك تريد الخروج فجأة.
There are shops downstairs.
هناك متاجر في الطابق السفلي.
That means there might be cockroaches in the house.
هذا يعني أنه قد يكون هناك صراصير في المنزل.
It's okay. If you mind,
لا بأس.  إذا سمحت،
we can see other houses
يمكننا أن نرى منازل أخرى
without shops.
بدون محلات.
That's not okay either.
هذا ليس جيدًا أيضًا.
What if he gets hungry at night?
ماذا لو جاع في الليل؟
What?
ماذا؟
Does he have to go all the way to eat?
هل عليه أن يذهب كل الطريق ليأكل؟
Well...
حسنًا...
He can order takeout.
يمكنه طلب تناول الطعام بالخارج.
It's easy.
من السهل.
In the middle of the night,
في منتصف الليل،
it's dangerous
انه خطير
for a boy to open his door
للصبي لفتح بابه
for strangers.
للغرباء.
It's fine.
لا بأس.
Let's go upstairs and take a look first.
دعنا نذهب إلى الطابق العلوي ونلقي نظرة أولاً.
Come on.
تعال.
Please.
لو سمحت.
This way, please.
من هذا الاتجاه من فضلك.
You are already here.
أنت هنا بالفعل.
[Block B of Fuguo Building]
[بلوك B من مبنى Fuguo]
Please.
لو سمحت.
How is it, Miss?
كيف الحال يا آنسة؟
This is the 17th house
هذا هو البيت السابع عشر
we've seen today.
رأيناه اليوم.
Is this a place for people?
هل هذا مكان للناس؟
It may be shabby,
قد يكون رثًا ،
but the facilities around it are very complete.
لكن المرافق المحيطة به كاملة للغاية.
What's the use of it?
ما فائدته؟
Is it for the convenience of rushing to the hospital
هل من اجل راحة الاسراع الى المستشفى
after he gets ill here?
بعد أن يمرض هنا؟
Yes, you are right.
نعم كلامك صحيح.
The hospital is just across the street.
المستشفى على الجانب الآخر من الشارع.
You can walk to the hospital in three minutes.
يمكنك المشي إلى المستشفى في ثلاث دقائق.
I know.
أنا أعرف.
It's the hospital where Deng Shuling works.
إنها المستشفى التي يعمل فيها دنغ شولينغ.
This is the place Aunt Shuling passes by after work.
هذا هو المكان الذي تمر به العمة شولينج بعد العمل.
This house is too shabby.
هذا المنزل رث جدا.
It's not okay.
هذا ليس مقبولا.
This is it.
هذه هي.
What?
ماذا؟
I said I want to live in this house.
قلت إنني أريد أن أعيش في هذا المنزل.
This is it.
هذه هي.
Are you sure?
هل أنت متأكد؟
Yes.
نعم.
She's asleep. Don't worry.
انها نائمة.  لا تقلق.
How is it at your place?
كيف هو مكانك؟
Everything is fine.
كل شيء على ما يرام.
I saw Hyperspace written by
رأيت Hyperspace من تأليف
Michio Kaku
ميتشيو كاكو
at the doorway of Qi Yue's room.
عند مدخل غرفة Qi Yue.
I believe all the speculations in the book.
أعتقد أن كل التكهنات الواردة في الكتاب.
Just like what Michio Kaku said,
تمامًا مثل ما قاله ميتشيو كاكو ،
physical law tells us what's possible,
يخبرنا القانون الفيزيائي ما هو ممكن ،
not what's feasible.
ليس ما هو ممكن.
Oh no.
أوه لا.
The photo.
الصورة.
[Qi Shuo]
[كي شو]
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
You can't keep your son with you when he grows up.
لا يمكنك إبقاء ابنك معك عندما يكبر.
You are hiding from me, right?
أنت تختبئ عني ، أليس كذلك؟
If you still don't reply to my messages,
إذا كنت لا تزال لا ترد على رسائلي ،
I'll come to you.
سوف آتي اليك.
I'm busy outside.
أنا مشغول بالخارج.
Let's talk later.
لنتحدث لاحقا.
You didn't answer my calls or reply to my messages.
لم ترد على مكالماتي أو ترد على رسائلي.
As a woman, my sixth sense tells me
كامرأة ، يخبرني حاستي السادسة
you're hiding from me.
أنت تختبئ مني.
Did your sixth sense tell you
هل أخبرك حاستك السادسة
men also need space to be alone?
الرجال أيضا بحاجة إلى مساحة ليكونوا بمفردهم؟
Why did you buy so many things again?
لماذا اشتريت الكثير من الأشياء مرة أخرى؟
To show my constant care about you.
لأظهر اهتمامي المستمر بك.
Here.
هنا.
You care about me or I care about you?
أنت تهتم بي أم أنا أهتم بك؟
Look at your house.
انظر إلى منزلك.
The light is bad.
الضوء سيء.
The curtains don't block out the light.
الستائر لا تحجب الضوء.
And the walls.
والجدران.
Should I change the wallpaper for you?
هل يجب أن أغير الخلفية من أجلك؟
Right?
يمين؟
You can just find a decoration team.
يمكنك فقط العثور على فريق الديكور.
It's such a nice day.
إنه يوم جميل.
Why are you here
لماذا أنت هنا
instead of going out with Lu Xiao?
بدلا من الخروج مع لو شياو؟
We...
نحن...
are already on the track of fate.
هم بالفعل على طريق القدر.
No need to rush it.
لا داعي للاندفاع.
The track of fate?
مسار القدر؟
Well said.
احسنت القول.
How has it been between you and Lu Xiao recently?
كيف كان الأمر بينك وبين لو شياو مؤخرًا؟
Didn't I tell you
ألم أخبرك
there is something wrong with your house's Feng Shui?
هل هناك شيء خاطئ في فنغ شوي في منزلك؟
It's an independent building.
إنه مبنى مستقل.
It's at the corner of the street.
إنه في زاوية الشارع.
It's like thousands of arrows piercing the heart.
إنها مثل آلاف الأسهم التي تخترق القلب.
I see.
أرى.
I'll find you a Feng Shui master.
سوف أجد لك سيد فنغ شوي.
Mom, mom, mom.
أمي أمي أمي.
Don't find me a Feng Shui master.
لا تجد لي سيد فنغ شوي.
Whether it's thousands of arrows piercing the heart depends on
يعتمد ما إذا كانت آلاف الأسهم التي تخترق القلب
how your relationship with Lu Xiao develops.
كيف تتطور علاقتك مع لو شياو.
Okay?
تمام؟
It's okay.
لا بأس.
Go on a date with Lu Xiao.
اذهب في موعد مع لو شياو.
Don't waste your time here.
لا تضيعوا وقتكم هنا.
You should trust your mom.
يجب أن تثق بأمك.
I trust you, mom.
أنا أثق بك يا أمي.
I won't do anything bad to you.
لن أفعل أي شيء سيء لك.
Trust your son once. Just go.
ثق بابنك مرة واحدة.  فقط اذهب.
Really. I won't do anything bad to you.
حقًا.  لن أفعل أي شيء سيء لك.
Trust me. I trust you.
ثق بي.  أنا أثق بك.
Okay?
تمام؟
Bye.
الوداع.
Trust me.
ثق بي.
Okay? Trust me.
تمام؟  ثق بي.
Bye.
الوداع.
Eat well, son.
كل جيدا يا بني.
Okay, okay.
حسنا حسنا.
Dad, I'm at my classmate's house.
أبي ، أنا في منزل زميلي في الفصل.
Did you go to the wrong door again?
هل ذهبت إلى الباب الخطأ مرة أخرى؟
No.
لا.
Isn't this the sixth floor?
أليس هذا هو الطابق السادس؟
It is.
إنها.
Uncle.
عم.
Uncle, I'm Qi Yue's classmate.
العم ، أنا زميل Qi Yue.
I'm Lu Xiao.
أنا لو شياو.
Aren't you Yue's boyfriend?
ألست صديق يو؟
We had a meal together.
تناولنا وجبة معا.
You are young but forgetful.
أنت شاب لكنك متناسق.
Come in.
ادخل.
Mr. Qi,
السيد تشي ،
you are not going back to the company this afternoon, right?
لن تعود إلى الشركة بعد ظهر اليوم ، أليس كذلك؟
Mr. Wang from Boyue came to visit you.
جاء السيد وانغ من Boyue لزيارتك.
Who is he?
من هو؟
You met him at the forum last time.
لقد قابلته في المنتدى آخر مرة.
I saw him last time?
رأيته آخر مرة؟
Yes.
نعم.
Take care of him.
الاعتناء به.
OK, Mr. Qi.
حسنًا ، سيد تشي.
Bye.
الوداع.
You are...
أنت...
Uncle, my name is Lu Xiao.
عمي ، اسمي لو شياو.
I'm asking if you want tea or wine.
أنا أسأل إذا كنت تريد الشاي أو النبيذ.
It's okay, uncle. I'm not thirsty.
لا بأس يا عمي.  انا لست عطشان.
I'm just afraid that you can't remember me.
أنا فقط أخشى ألا تتذكرني.
I remember you.
انا اتذكرك.
You are 188cm tall and at the same age as Yue.
يبلغ طولك 188 سم وفي نفس عمر Yue.
You major in physics, and your dad is a teacher.
أنت تتخصص في الفيزياء ، ووالدك مدرس.
Your home is at No. 51 Anzhen Road in Linjiang District.
يقع منزلك في شارع Anzhen رقم 51 في منطقة Linjiang.
You remember it so clearly.
تتذكرها بوضوح.
Yes.
نعم.
I haven't forgotten, have I?
أنا لم أنس ، أليس كذلك؟
I understand you young people.
أفهمكم أيها الشباب.
But let me tell you,
ولكن اسمحوا لي ان اقول لكم،
I was more nervous than you
كنت متوترا أكثر منك
when I first went to the house of Yue's mother.
عندما ذهبت لأول مرة إلى منزل والدة يوي.
You remember what happened so long ago?
هل تتذكر ما حدث منذ زمن بعيد؟
Yes.
نعم.
Every memory is precious.
كل ذكرى ثمينة.
It can't be lost.
لا يمكن أن تضيع.
But
لكن
why are you acting weird today?
لماذا تتصرف بغرابة اليوم؟
It's because they said you...
هذا لأنهم قالوا لك ...
What did Yue say about me?
ماذا قال يو عني؟
What did they say?
ماذا قالوا؟
They said you have Alzheimer's disease.
قالوا إنك مصاب بمرض الزهايمر.
That brat.
أن شقي.
How could she say that about her father?
كيف تقول ذلك عن والدها؟
You just said "they".
لقد قلت "هم" للتو.
Who are they?
من هؤلاء؟
Qi Shuo.
تشي شو.
Her tutor.
مدرسها.
Her cousin.
ابن عمها.
Who is he?
من هو؟
That brat.
أن شقي.
She said I have Alzheimer's disease.
قالت إنني أعاني من مرض الزهايمر.
And she lied to me about her tutor.
وكذبت علي بشأن مدرسها.
Tutor?
مدرس خاص؟
Alzheimer's disease?
مرض الزهايمر؟
Oh no.
أوه لا.
He knows.
هو يعرف.
Come out! You brat.
يخرج!  أنت شقي.
You won't come out?
لن تخرج؟
Fine. I'll teach you a lesson when you come home.
بخير.  سأعلمك درسًا عندما تعود إلى المنزل.
Do we know each other?
هل نعرف بعضنا؟
No.
لا.
But I believe
لكن انا اؤمن
we will become good friends soon.
سوف نصبح أصدقاء حميمين قريبا.
Although I'm her cousin,
على الرغم من أنني ابن عمها ،
don't you feel uncomfortable
ألا تشعر بعدم الارتياح
if your girlfriend
إذا كانت صديقتك
lives with a man every day?
يعيش مع رجل كل يوم؟
You're here.
أنت هنا.
Why didn't you answer my call?
لماذا لم ترد على مكالمتي؟
My phone died.
انتهي شحن هاتفي.
I went to my friend's house.
ذهبت الى منزل أصدقائي.
Have you eaten?
هل أكلت؟
Did you go to Qi Shuo's place?
هل ذهبت إلى مكان Qi Shuo؟
I was worried that he's not used to living alone.
كنت قلقة من أنه لم يعتاد العيش بمفرده.
And I didn't want you to worry.
وأنا لا أريدك أن تقلق.
That's why I didn't tell you.
لهذا لم أخبرك.
You went to your cousin's house.
لقد ذهبت إلى منزل ابن عمك.
Why should I worry?
لماذا علي القلق؟
Unless he's not your cousin.
إلا إذا لم يكن ابن عمك.
What are you talking about?
عن ماذا تتحدث؟
Qi Yue.
تشي يو.
There is a scientific theory in biology
توجد نظرية علمية في علم الأحياء
called feedback loop.
تسمى حلقة التغذية الراجعة.
In life, it generally means
في الحياة ، هذا يعني بشكل عام
when something happens,
عندما يحدث شيء ما ،
the same thing will happen again
نفس الشيء سيحدث مرة أخرى
and will happen faster.
وسيحدث بشكل أسرع.
It's like someone subconsciously uses a lie
يبدو الأمر كما لو أن شخصًا ما يستخدم كذبة دون وعي
to patch up another lie.
لإصلاح كذبة أخرى.
But it's only snowballing.
لكنها تتعاظم فقط.
It will only make things worse.
وسوف يزيد الأمور إلا سوءا.
Yes.
نعم.
I lied to you.
لقد كذبت عليك.
My dad didn't have
والدي لم يكن لديه
Alzheimer's disease.
مرض الزهايمر.
I just don't want you to see
أنا فقط لا أريدك أن ترى
I have a cold-hearted father.
لدي أب بارد القلب.
That's why I said that.
لهذا قلت ذلك.
Your father is not cold-hearted at all.
والدك ليس بارد القلب على الإطلاق.
He cares about you
انه يهتم لأمرك
and remembers everything about you,
ويتذكر كل شيء عنك ،
including your tutor, Qi Shuo.
بما في ذلك مدرسك ، تشي شو.
Tutor?
مدرس خاص؟
What tutor? Who said that?
ما المعلم؟  من قال هذا؟
Qi Yue.
تشي يو.
Why did you lie to me?
لماذا كذبت علي؟
I told you.
أخبرتك.
I lied about my dad.
لقد كذبت بشأن والدي.
Who is Qi Shuo exactly?
من هو Qi Shuo بالضبط؟
Why?
لماذا؟
If he is your admirer,
إذا كان معجبًا بك ،
why did he try so hard
لماذا حاول جاهدا
to let us be together?
لنكن معا؟
If he is really your cousin,
إذا كان حقًا ابن عمك ،
why doesn't your father
لماذا لا والدك
know him at all?
تعرفه على الإطلاق؟
Qi Shuo
تشي شو
is my cousin.
هو ابن عمي.
Qi Yue, I find that I don't know you at all.
Qi Yue ، أجد أنني لا أعرفك على الإطلاق.
I think trust is the basis
أعتقد أن الثقة هي الأساس
for two people to be together.
لشخصين ليكونا معا.
I never doubted you.
أنا لم أشك فيك أبدا.
But you don't seem to believe me.
لكن يبدو أنك لا تصدقني.
I've always trusted you.
لطالما وثقت بك.
Qi Yue.
تشي يو.
Did you conspire together to trick me
هل تآمرت معا لخداعني
from the beginning?
من البداية؟
I know.
أنا أعرف.
Have a good rest.
لديها راحة جيدة.
Goodbye.
مع السلامة.
Qi Shuo is our son.
Qi Shuo هو ابننا.
What are you talking about?
عن ماذا تتحدث؟
He came
لقد اتى
from 30 years later
بعد 30 عامًا
through a time machine.
من خلال آلة الزمن.
What did you say?
ماذا قلت؟
Shuling.
شالينج.
Dr. Han.
دكتور.  هو.
Why did you get off work so early today?
لماذا توقفت عن العمل مبكرًا اليوم؟
Let's walk together.
دعونا نسير معا.
Okay.
تمام.
Not everything can be predicted.
لا يمكن توقع كل شيء.
Is it right or wrong?
هل هذا صحيح أو خاطئ؟
That's it.
هذا كل شيء.
The time travel you expect
السفر عبر الزمن الذي تتوقعه
[DNA Identification of Qi Yue and Qi Shuo]
[تحديد الحمض النووي لـ Qi Yue و Qi Shuo]
will be realized in 30 years.
سيتم تحقيقه في غضون 30 عامًا.
[The probability of being his mother is 99.9999%.]
[نسبة احتمال أن تكوني والدته هي 99.9999٪.]
The first one to experience it
أول من جربها
is our future son.
هو ابننا المستقبلي.
There is an official seal. It's legal.
هناك ختم رسمي.  إنه قانوني.
You said
أنت قلت
Qi Shuo is our
Qi Shuo هو منتجنا
son?
ابن؟
I know it sounds absurd.
أعلم أنه يبدو سخيفًا.
When I first heard it from Qi Shuo,
عندما سمعته لأول مرة من Qi Shuo ،
my reaction was exactly like yours.
كان رد فعلي مشابهاً لك تمامًا.
You also mentioned
ذكرت أيضا
a time machine.
آلة الزمن.
Yes.
نعم.
How is that possible?
كيف يعقل ذلك؟
Time travel can only send people
السفر عبر الزمن يمكن أن يرسل الناس فقط
to someone else's future.
لمستقبل شخص آخر.
There is no theoretical logic like going back.
لا يوجد منطق نظري مثل العودة.
And all this
وكل هذا
is just a fantasy experiment.
هي مجرد تجربة خيالية.
But that's the truth.
لكن هذه هي الحقيقة.
Okay.
تمام.
Well.
حسنًا.
Even if he really came back
حتى لو عاد حقًا
from 30 years later,
بعد 30 عامًا ،
why did he do that?
لماذا فعل ذلك
He told me
قال لي
to pursue you again
لمطاردتك مرة أخرى
to change fate.
لتغيير المصير.
Change whose fate?
تغيير مصير من؟
Mine.
مِلكِي.
So,
لذا،
he arranged all this?
رتب كل هذا؟
You pursued me and stay with me
أنت تلاحقني وتبقى معي
just to change your fate?
فقط لتغيير مصيرك؟
That's true.
هذا صحيح.
But not really true.
لكن هذا ليس صحيحًا حقًا.
Well.
حسنًا.
It was like this at first.
كان مثل هذا في البداية.
But later,
ولكن في وقت لاحق،
my love for you has nothing to do with others.
حبي لك لا علاقة له بالآخرين.
It has nothing to do with that stupid fate either.
لا علاقة له بهذا المصير الغبي أيضًا.
Faster than the speed of light. Shrinkage.
أسرع من سرعة الضوء.  انكماش.
The Casimir effect.
تأثير كازيمير.
I know it's hard for you to accept this.
أعلم أنه من الصعب عليك قبول هذا.
Qi Yue,
تشي يو ،
you said a lot today.
قلت الكثير اليوم.
I don't know what your purpose is,
لا أعرف ما هو هدفك ،
but I really can't accept it.
لكنني حقًا لا يمكنني قبول ذلك.
What purpose can I have?
ما هو الغرض الذي يمكنني الحصول عليه؟
You saw it
أنت رأيته
with your own eyes.
بأم عينيك.
I think
أظن
I'll go back first.
سأعود أولا.
I knew it.
كنت أعرف.
We all believe that one day,
كلنا نعتقد أنه يومًا ما ،
humans will realize time travel.
سوف يدرك البشر السفر عبر الزمن.
We meet again.
نلتقي مرة أخرى.
You are
أنت
Qi Yue's cousin?
ابن عم تشي يو؟
Yes.
نعم.
Lu Xiao,
لو شياو
I have something to ask you.
لدي شيء أن أسألك.
When will we have a son?
متى سيكون لدينا ابن؟
But he's not your son.
لكنه ليس ابنك.
You're not his mother either.
أنت لست والدته أيضًا.
Don't you want to know
لا تريد أن تعرف
what our future son looks like?
كيف يبدو ابننا المستقبلي؟
Didn't we agree
ألم نتفق
to get used to a life with a son
لتعتاد على الحياة مع الابن
in advance?
مقدماً؟
You came to me at this time
أتيت إلي في هذا الوقت
because of time travel?
بسبب السفر عبر الزمن؟
Professor, I'm really sorry
أستاذ ، أنا آسف حقًا
to bother you at this time.
ليضايقك في هذا الوقت.
But this is really important to me.
لكن هذا مهم حقًا بالنسبة لي.
You know
أنت تعرف
time and space can't be separated
لا يمكن فصل الزمان والمكان
in time travel.
في السفر عبر الزمن.
I know.
أنا أعرف.
But according to the Theory of Relativity,
لكن وفقًا لنظرية النسبية ،
if humans can really go faster than the speed of light,
إذا كان بإمكان البشر فعلاً التحرك بسرعة أكبر من سرعة الضوء ،
maybe we can go back to the past.
ربما يمكننا العودة إلى الماضي.
Is that so?
هل هذا صحيح؟
This theory
هذه النظرية
is contradictory.
متناقض.
They just overturned the theory.
لقد قلبوا النظرية للتو.
You said "they"?
قلت "هم"؟
Yes. There is a group of elite scientists
نعم.  هناك مجموعة من نخبة العلماء
in the cutting-edge science field
في مجال العلوم المتطورة
studying this topic.
دراسة هذا الموضوع.
I think
أظن
maybe in 30 years,
ربما في غضون 30 عامًا ،
humans can really realize time travel.
يمكن للبشر أن يدركوا حقًا السفر عبر الزمن.
30 years?
30 سنه؟
They can not only go to the future,
لا يمكنهم فقط الذهاب إلى المستقبل ،
but also go back to the past
ولكن أيضًا نعود إلى الماضي
to change fate.
لتغيير المصير.
What you said is great.
ما قلته رائع.
Your confidence is needed in the scientific research field.
ثقتكم مطلوبة في مجال البحث العلمي.
Just a guess, Professor.
مجرد تخمين يا أستاذ.
I need to explain it to her.
أحتاج أن أشرحها لها.
[Institute of Oncology  Senior Ward Building]
[مبنى الجناح الأول لمعهد الأورام]
Maybe I should tell her after she gets off work.
ربما يجب أن أخبرها بعد خروجها من العمل.
Will it affect her work now?
هل سيؤثر على عملها الآن؟
Xu Zhaoyang.
شو تشاويانغ.
Why is he following Aunt Shuling?
لماذا يتابع عمته شولينج؟
Why isn't he answering my call?
لماذا لا يرد على مكالمتي؟
Qi Shuo.
تشي شو.
There is medical trouble on the second floor. Come quickly.
هناك مشكلة طبية في الطابق الثاني.  تعال بسرعة.
Hurry up.
أسرع - بسرعة.
Just go. Stop looking.
فقط اذهب.  توقف عن النظر.
I heard that a college student
سمعت أن طالب جامعي
stabbed a nurse with a knife.
طعن ممرضة بسكين.
Although this report
على الرغم من أن هذا التقرير
is from a private identification center,
من مركز تحديد الهوية الخاص ،
according to Mendel's Laws of Inheritance
وفقًا لقوانين الميراث مندل
and test results,
ونتائج الاختبار ،
Qi Shuo's genetic type
النوع الجيني Qi Shuo
coincides with Qi Yue's genetic condition.
يتزامن مع الحالة الوراثية لـ Qi Yue.
The parental probability is 99.99%.
احتمالية الأبوين هي 99.99٪.
It meets the criteria of DNA tests.
يفي بمعايير اختبارات الحمض النووي.
Xu Zhaoyang.
شو تشاويانغ.
Qi Shuo.
تشي شو.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Deng Shuling.
دنغ شولينج.
Damn you!
اللعنة عليك!
Stop fighting!
وقف القتال!
Just go.
فقط اذهب.
Stop looking.
توقف عن النظر.
Mr. Xu.
السيد شو.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
He...
هو...
He's my friend.
إنه صديقي.
Well.
حسنًا.
Shouldn't he take legal responsibility
ألا يجب أن يتحمل المسؤولية القانونية
for assaulting people randomly?
لاعتداء الناس عشوائيا؟
I apologize to you.
انا اعتذر لك.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
What's the use of the police if an apology is useful?
ما فائدة الشرطة إذا كان الاعتذار مفيدًا؟
I'll pay for your medical bills.
سأدفع فواتيرك الطبية.
As a medical worker,
كعامل طبي ،
shouldn't you deal with your love issue
ألا يجب أن تتعامل مع قضية حبك
first?
أولاً؟
I'm sorry, Mr. Xu.
أنا آسف ، السيد شو.
It's my fault.
هذا خطأي.
[Don't be angry.]
[لا تغضب.]
Thank you for dealing with my wound.
شكرا لك على التعامل مع جرحي.
I'll just pretend that
سوف أتظاهر بذلك
nothing happened today.
لم يحدث شيء اليوم.
But you should take care of him in the future.
لكن يجب أن تعتني به في المستقبل.
I'm speechless.
أنا عاجز عن الكلام.
Do you believe me now?
هل تصدقني الآن؟
I didn't lie.
أنا لم أكذب.
Why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
I'm looking for Qi Shuo.
أنا أبحث عن Qi Shuo.
You know he's here?
هل تعلم أنه هنا؟
Now
الآن
I might need to explain it with telepathy between a mother and a son.
قد أحتاج إلى شرح ذلك عن طريق التخاطر بين الأم والابن.
Does Qi Shuo
هل تشى شو
always fight with others
دائما القتال مع الآخرين
for no reason?
بلا سبب؟
He just doesn't like Xu Zhaoyang.
إنه فقط لا يحب Xu Zhaoyang.
If I don't like someone,
إذا كنت لا أحب شخصًا ما ،
I should stay away from him
يجب أن أبتعد عنه
instead of
بدلاً من
fighting.
قتال.
You still don't believe me, do you?
ما زلت لا تصدقني ، أليس كذلك؟
I'm not.
أنالست.
I understand.
أفهم.
Everyone needs time to accept it.
كل شخص يحتاج إلى وقت لقبوله.
A 25-year-old man
رجل عمره 25 سنة
suddenly stood in front of you
فجأة وقفت أمامك
to tell you that he is your son.
لأخبرك أنه ابنك.
Everyone has to convince himself.
على الجميع أن يقنع نفسه.
Is there a party in the hospital today?
هل يوجد حفل في المستشفى اليوم؟
Why are you all here?
لماذا أنتم جميعا هنا؟
He knows everything.
إنه يعرف كل شيء.
Know what?
تعرف ماذا؟
Everything.
كل شئ.
If you're free later,
إذا كنت متفرغًا لاحقًا ،
let's go home and watch a movie.
دعنا نذهب إلى المنزل ومشاهدة فيلم.
He...
هو...
A family should be together.
يجب أن تكون الأسرة معًا.
Wait.
انتظر.
Why didn't you tell me in advance?
لماذا لم تخبرني مسبقا؟
Why didn't you answer my call?
لماذا لم ترد على مكالمتي؟
He knows everything?
إنه يعرف كل شيء؟
Yes.
نعم.
Including I came here from 30 years later?
بما في ذلك جئت إلى هنا بعد 30 عامًا؟
Including I'm your son?
بما في ذلك أنا ابنك؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
What do you think "everything" means?
ما رأيك يعني "كل شيء"؟
Then why is he so calm?
إذن لماذا هو هادئ جدا؟
This may be the style of a mature man.
قد يكون هذا هو أسلوب الرجل الناضج.
Why didn't you inherit
لماذا لم ترث
his excellent genes?
جيناته الممتازة؟
Silly son.
ابن سخيف.
You...
أنت...
You call this maturity?
هل تسمي هذا النضج؟
What a day.
يا له من يوم.
Come on, what do you want to watch?
هيا ، ماذا تريد أن تشاهد؟
About Time.
حول الوقت.
Dune.
الكثيب.
I thought you like science fiction films.
اعتقدت أنك تحب أفلام الخيال العلمي.
Why do you think so?
لماذا تظن ذلك؟
Now, the minority obeys the majority.
الآن ، الأقلية تطيع الأغلبية.
The margarine in popcorn
المارجرين في الفشار
contains trans-fatty acids.
يحتوي على الأحماض الدهنية غير المشبعة.
Eating too much will increase the risk of the coronary heart disease.
إن الإفراط في تناول الطعام يزيد من خطر الإصابة بأمراض القلب التاجية.
Just some popcorn.
فقط بعض الفشار.
Why are you so serious?
لماذا انت جاد جدا
They do have much in common.
لديهم الكثير من القواسم المشتركة.
But is he really my son?
ولكن هل هو حقا ابني؟
Enjoy your life, son.
استمتع بحياتك يا بني.
You really have inherited my genes.
لقد ورثت جيناتي حقًا.
Why aren't you crying?
لماذا لا تبكين
Why should I cry?
لماذا علي البكاء؟
Why do you always cry?
لماذا تبكي دائما؟
Aren't you the same?
ألست أنت نفس الشيء؟
We travel in time
نسافر في الوقت المناسب
as we live our life every day.
كما نعيش حياتنا كل يوم.
What we can do is to do our best
ما يمكننا القيام به هو بذل قصارى جهدنا
to cherish
لنعتز به
this extraordinary journey of life.
هذه الرحلة غير العادية للحياة.
Look.
ينظر.
The leading actor in the movie also went back through time travel
كما عاد الممثل الرئيسي في الفيلم من خلال السفر عبر الزمن
to change many things.
لتغيير أشياء كثيرة.
Isn't this what we're experiencing now?
أليس هذا ما نشهده الآن؟
Yes.
نعم.
The movie says love can't be changed.
يقول الفيلم أن الحب لا يمكن تغييره.
So you and Lu Xiao are destined lovers.
لذلك أنت و لو شياو محبين متجهين.
So we must do like they do in the movie.
لذلك يجب أن نفعل كما يفعلون في الفيلم.
You should cherish this journey.
يجب أن تعتز بهذه الرحلة.
Cherish me and Lu Xiao.
نعتز بي ولو شياو.
Although
بالرغم من
we will meet in the future,
سوف نلتقي في المستقبل ،
why do I suddenly feel
لماذا أشعر فجأة
I can't bear to part with you?
لا استطيع تحمل الانفصال عنك؟
It's okay.
لا بأس.
Don't cry.
لا تبكي.
Where's Lu Xiao?
أين لو شياو؟
Did you cry stealthily in the bathroom?
هل بكيت خلسة في الحمام؟
Yes.
نعم.
I'm always slow.
أنا دائما بطيء.
Lu Xiao,
لو شياو
I know it's hard for you to accept all this now.
أعلم أنه من الصعب عليك قبول كل هذا الآن.
But that's the truth.
لكن هذه هي الحقيقة.
We are destined to be together.
نحن مقدرون أن نكون معا.
Destined?
مقدر؟
How about
ماذا عن
you start to know each other
تبدأ في معرفة بعضكما البعض
with your new identities now?
بهوياتك الجديدة الآن؟
How?
كيف؟
You decide.
انت صاحب القرار.
I...
أنا...
I don't have a clue.
ليس لدي دليل.
But
لكن
like you said,
مثلما قلت،
a family
عائلة
should be together no matter what.
يجب أن نكون معًا مهما كان الأمر.
Allow me.
اسمح لي.
My future husband.
زوجي المستقبلي.
This is my future son.
هذا ابني المستقبلي.
Hello.
مرحبًا.
Her future husband.
زوجها المستقبلي.
My future...
مستقبلي...
son.
ابن.
Please read carefully before donating your blood
يرجى القراءة بعناية قبل التبرع بدمك
and answer all the questions in the questionnaire.
والإجابة على جميع الأسئلة الواردة في الاستبيان.
There are so many questions on it.
هناك الكثير من الأسئلة حول هذا الموضوع.
Do you all know someone
هل تعلمون كلكم أحدا
through this kind of charity project?
من خلال هذا النوع من المشاريع الخيرية؟
That is so strange.
هذا غريب جدا
Any other questions?
أي أسئلة أخرى؟
No.
لا.
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
I...
أنا...
I have a phobia about needles.
لدي رهاب من الإبر.
In that case,
في هذه الحالة،
we shouldn't donate blood.
لا يجب أن نتبرع بالدم.
If an adult donates 400 ml of blood a year,
إذا تبرع شخص بالغ بـ 400 مل من الدم سنويًا ،
it will stimulate the hemopoiesis function of bone marrow
سوف يحفز وظيفة تكوين الدم في نخاع العظام
and create new blood.
وخلق دماء جديدة.
In that case,
في هذه الحالة،
this should become our family tradition.
يجب أن يصبح هذا تقليد عائلتنا.
Do you know your blood type?
هل تعرف فصيلة دمك؟
Yes. O.
نعم.  س.
It suddenly occurs to me that
فجأة يحدث لي ذلك
I have something to do in the lab.
لدي شيء لأفعله في المختبر.
I need to go back.
أنا بحاجة للعودة.
I'll go to the lab with you.
سأذهب إلى المختبر معك.
I have gastroenteritis again.
أعاني من التهاب المعدة والأمعاء مرة أخرى.
I need to go to the bathroom.
يجب ان اذهب الى الحمام.
I'll go to the bathroom with you first.
سأذهب إلى الحمام معك أولاً.
We'll donate blood when we're back.
سنتبرع بالدم عندما نعود.
I see.
أرى.
You still don't want to accept the fact.
ما زلت لا تريد قبول الحقيقة.
I'm not.
أنالست.
My blood type is O.
فصيلة دمي هي O.
Your blood type is AB.
فصيلة دمك هي AB.
Qi Shuo.
تشي شو.
I'm 2B.
أنا 2 ب.
Go for a blood test if you don't believe me.
اذهب لإجراء فحص دم إذا كنت لا تصدقني.
-I'm not going. -I'm not going.
-أنا لن أذهب.  -أنا لن أذهب.
Look.
ينظر.
You two are exactly the same.
أنتما الاثنان متماثلان تمامًا.
[Yulin Ueno Bookstore]
[مكتبة يولين أوينو]
Hello, madam.
مرحبا سيدتي.
Your Americano.
أمريكانو الخاص بك.
With so much sugar,
مع الكثير من السكر
aren't you afraid of diabetes?
الا تخاف من مرض السكر
It's too bitter. Can't I put in some sugar?
إنه مرير للغاية.  لا يمكنني وضع بعض السكر؟
Why are you mad at me?
لماذا أنت جنون في وجهي؟
Lu Xiao doesn't believe me.
لو شياو لا تصدقني.
He just doesn't want to be with me.
هو فقط لا يريد أن يكون معي.
No matter
لا يهم
who it is,
من هو،
he won't believe it right away, right?
لن يصدق ذلك على الفور ، أليس كذلك؟
But why do I believe it?
لكن لماذا أصدق ذلك؟
Are you sure?
هل أنت متأكد؟
Did you forgot the ancient way of
هل نسيت الطريقة القديمة
mixing blood to see if people are related?
خلط الدم لمعرفة ما إذا كان الناس مرتبطين؟
Besides, with his current topic, Lu Xiao has 10,000 ways
إلى جانب ذلك ، مع موضوعه الحالي ، لدى لو شياو 10000 طريقة
to verify the feasibility
للتحقق من الجدوى
of time travel.
من السفر عبر الزمن.
Then why does he still suspect it?
ثم لماذا لا يزال يشك في ذلك؟
Because he also has emotions apart from theories.
لأنه أيضًا لديه مشاعر بصرف النظر عن النظريات.
Emotionally,
عاطفيا
if a son seven years older than him suddenly appeared
إذا ظهر فجأة ابن أكبر منه بسبع سنوات
and told you
وأخبرتك
you had to pursue him to change your fate,
كان عليك أن تلاحقه لتغيير مصيرك ،
no one would believe it
لن يصدقها أحد
immediately
في الحال
and remain calm in his heart.
ويبقى هادئا في قلبه.
That's true.
هذا صحيح.
Of course.
بالطبع.
It means he values your relationship
هذا يعني أنه يقدر علاقتك
and your future.
ومستقبلك.
According to what you said,
حسب ما قلته
I'm quite happy.
انا سعيد جدا.
Do you remember the line in About Time?
هل تتذكر السطر في "حول الوقت"؟
Live every day carefully and enjoy every day.
عش كل يوم بعناية واستمتع بكل يوم.
Take every day
خذ كل يوم
as the last day of an ordinary life.
كآخر يوم في حياة عادية.
I'll send him a WeChat message to apologize.
سأرسل له رسالة WeChat للاعتذار.
Don't.
لا.
I'm his son.
أنا ابنه.
I know him better.
أنا أعرفه أكثر.
I'll talk to him.
سوف اتحدث معه.
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
Don't you have anything
ليس لديك أي شيء
to ask me?
ليسألني؟
I have.
أملك.
If
لو
I didn't throw it out,
لم أرميها ،
the chain wouldn't have fallen, right?
السلسلة لم تكن لتقع ، أليس كذلك؟
What kind of boring question is this?
أي نوع من الأسئلة الممل هذا؟
Even if we go back to the past,
حتى لو عدنا إلى الماضي ،
we can't change what will happen next.
لا يمكننا تغيير ما سيحدث بعد ذلك.
But if you didn't put this chain
لكن إذا لم تضع هذه السلسلة
into this cup,
في هذا الكوب ،
the experiment would no longer exist.
التجربة لم تعد موجودة.
Everything happens for a reason.
كل شيء يحدث لسبب ما.
There are reasons for the reason.
هناك أسباب للسبب.
There is no end to it.
ليس هناك حد لذلك.
Everything
كل شئ
has been decided
تقرر
in the beginning.
في البداية.
You theorists are so annoying.
أنتم المنظرين مزعجون للغاية.
Professor.
أستاذ.
This is the book I told you before.
هذا هو الكتاب الذي قلته لكم من قبل.
[Isaac Asimov: The End of Eternity]
[إسحاق أسيموف: نهاية الأبدية]
Even a famous science fiction writer
حتى كاتب خيال علمي مشهور
like Isaac Asimov
مثل اسحق اسيموف
couldn't explain
لا يمكن تفسيره
the grandfather paradox caused by time travel.
مفارقة الجد الناجمة عن السفر عبر الزمن.
You just made Qi Yue angry.
لقد أثارت غضب تشي يو للتو.
Do you know that?
هل تعرف أن؟
If I went back to two hours ago,
إذا عدت إلى ما قبل ساعتين ،
would Qi Yue not be angry?
لن يغضب Qi Yue؟
Or no matter what I do,
أو بغض النظر عما أفعله ،
nothing will change.
لن يتغير شيء.
What's wrong with you today?
ما هو الخطأ معك اليوم؟
Professor,
أستاذ،
I'm not feeling well today.
أنا لست على ما يرام اليوم.
I want to go back and read this book.
أريد أن أعود وأقرأ هذا الكتاب.
Okay, go.
حسنا اذهب.
Why are you two
لماذا أنتما الاثنان
studying time travel all of a sudden?
دراسة السفر عبر الزمن فجأة؟
It looks like there are many talented people for future scientific undertakings.
يبدو أن هناك العديد من الأشخاص الموهوبين للمهام العلمية المستقبلية.
Professor, I'm flattered.
أستاذ ، أنا أشعر بالإطراء.
I just...
أنا فقط...
We're not professional.
نحن لسنا محترفين.
Excuse me.
اعذرني.
It won't take too much time
لن يستغرق الأمر الكثير من الوقت
for Lu Xiao to figure out the truth.
لو شياو لمعرفة الحقيقة.
I'd better tell him everything.
من الأفضل أن أخبره بكل شيء.
Aunt Shuling.
العمة شولينج.
I'll pick you up after work.
سأقلك بعد العمل.
Did you eat vitamins?
هل اكلت فيتامينات؟
I threw away your instant noodles.
لقد تخلصت من المكرونة سريعة التحضير.
Tuantuan peed in my house again.
تبول Tuantuan في منزلي مرة أخرى.
Did you eat vitamins?
هل اكلت فيتامينات؟
I threw away your instant noodles.
لقد تخلصت من المكرونة سريعة التحضير.
Tuantuan peed in my house again.
تبول Tuantuan في منزلي مرة أخرى.
I'll pick you up after work.
سأقلك بعد العمل.
Did you eat vitamins?
هل اكلت فيتامينات؟
I threw away your instant noodles.
لقد تخلصت من المكرونة سريعة التحضير.
Tuantuan peed in my house again.
تبول Tuantuan في منزلي مرة أخرى.
Did you eat vitamins?
هل اكلت فيتامينات؟
I threw away your instant noodles.
لقد تخلصت من المكرونة سريعة التحضير.
Tuantuan peed in my house again.
تبول Tuantuan في منزلي مرة أخرى.
[I Belonged To Your World]
[أنتمي إلى عالمك]
[If I can't walk you home, no street lamps should be broken.]
[إذا لم أتمكن من إرشادك إلى المنزل ، فلا ينبغي أن تكسر مصابيح الشوارع.]
Come and take a look.
وتعالوا نلقي نظرة.
This lamp here
هذا المصباح هنا
doesn't work.
لا يعمل.
Is it for decoration?
هل هي للزينة؟
This door is forbidden.
هذا الباب ممنوع.
No one usually comes here.
لا أحد يأتي هنا عادة.
Isn't it a waste of power
أليس هذا مضيعة للقوة
if the lamp is on?
إذا كان المصباح مضاء؟
But we paid property management fees.
لكننا دفعنا رسوم إدارة الممتلكات.
Besides,
بجانب،
it's dark and unsafe.
إنه مظلم وغير آمن.
If you make it work,
إذا جعلتها تعمل ،
you can light up the way home for others.
يمكنك أن تضيء الطريق إلى المنزل للآخرين.
I'm just a property management staff member,
أنا مجرد موظف في إدارة الممتلكات ،
not a philanthropist.
ليس فاعل خير.
According to
وفق
the Law of
قانون
the Management of New Urban Residences,
إدارة المساكن الحضرية الجديدة ،
if the property management staff turn off the light in residences privately,
إذا قام موظفو إدارة الممتلكات بإطفاء الضوء في المساكن بشكل خاص ،
residents...
سكان ...
Don't.
لا.
It's just a piece of cake.
انها مجرد قطعة من الكعكة.
I'll turn on the light for you.
سوف أشعل الضوء لك.